// Contains all the questions, correct answers and the choices for each level of the game 

const grade1 = [
    {
        question: "What does demi plie mean?",
        correctAnswer: "Half bend",
        choices: ["Half bend", "Bend ", "Stretch", "Spring"]
    },
    {
        question: "What does tendu mean?",
        correctAnswer: "Taut or Tight",
        choices: ["Taut or Tight", "Sink or Bend", "Rise", "Spring"]
    },
    {
        question: "What does fondu mean?",
        correctAnswer: "Sink or Bend",
        choices: ["Sink or Bend", "Spring", "Taut or Tight", "Rise"]
    },
    {
        question: "What does saute mean?",
        correctAnswer: "To Spring",
        choices: ["To Spring", "To Rise", "To Bend", "To Skip"]
    },
    {
        question: "How many basic arm positions are there? ",
        correctAnswer: "5",
        choices: ["5","12","6","3"]
    },
]

const grade2 = [
    {
        question: "What does a terre mean?",
        correctAnswer: "On the ground ",
        choices: ["On the ground", "In the air", "To be lifted", "None"]
    },
    {
        question: "What is Demi Detourne?",
        correctAnswer: "Half turn",
        choices: ["Half turn", "Full turn", "Linked turn", "Double turn "]
    },
    {
        question: "What is a Chagement?",
        correctAnswer: "A spring from 5th to 5th position, changing feet",
        choices: ["A spring from 5th to 5th position, changing feet", "A spring from 3rd to 3rd position, changing feet", "A spring from 1st to 1st position, changing feet", "A spring from 4th to 4th position, changing feet"]
    },
    {
        question: "What are extreme ends of Rond de Jambe a terre?",
        correctAnswer: "4th position, devant, and derriere",
        choices: ["4th position, devant, and derriere", "5th position, devant, and derriere", "2nd position, devant, and derriere", "3rd position, devant, and derriere"]
    },
    {
        question: "In ballet terms, what happens to the feet in an Assemble",
        correctAnswer: "They should join together in the air before landing",
        choices: ["They should join together in the air before landing", "They shouldn't join together in the air before landing", "Assemble is not done in the air", "Theey should join in the air and come apart at landing"]
    },
]

const grade3 = [
    {
        question: "How many positions of the feet are there?",
        correctAnswer: "5",
        choices: ["5", "4", "6", "12"]
    },
    {
        question: "How should the weight of the body be distributed on the feet?",
        correctAnswer: "All three",
        choices: ["All three", "Big toe", "Little toe", "Heel"]
    },
    {
        question: "What does pirouette mean?",
        correctAnswer: "To turn",
        choices: ["To turn", "To spring", "To jump", "To leap"]
    },
    {
        question: "How many ways can you turn?",
        correctAnswer: "Endehors and Endedans",
        choices: ["Endehors and Endedans", "Endehors", "Endedans", "Neither"]
    },
    {
        question: "What is grand battement?",
        correctAnswer: "Throwing of leg into the air",
        choices: ["Throwing of leg into the air", "The step of the cat", "Beating and striking", "Unfolding leg into the air"]
    },
]

const grade4 = [
    {
        question: "What does pique mean?",
        correctAnswer: "Pick up sharply",
        choices: ["Pick up sharply", "Small beating", "To snatch", "To point"]
    },
    {
        question: "What does petit battement mean?",
        correctAnswer: "Small beating",
        choices: ["Small beating", "Beating", "Beating and Striking", "Striking"]
    },
    {
        question: "What is a glissade?",
        correctAnswer: "A step and a glide",
        choices: ["A step and a glide", "A step", "A glide", "A spring"]
    },
    {
        question: "Is an arabesque terre or en l’air?",
        correctAnswer: "Either",
        choices: ["Either", "Terre", "En l’air", "Neither "]
    },
    {
        question: "How many steps are in Pas de Bourree?",
        correctAnswer: "3",
        choices: ["3", "4", "2", "5"]
    },
]

const grade5 = [
    {
        question: "What is the meaning of coupe, fouette, raccourci",
        correctAnswer: "To cut, whip and return",
        choices: ["To cut, whip and return", "To step, spring, and return", " To whip, cut and return", "To  spring, step and return"]
    },
    {
        question: "What does serre mean?",
        correctAnswer: "Continuous",
        choices: ["Continuous", "Backwards", "Gliding", "Balance"]
    },
    {
        question: "What does tombe mean?",
        correctAnswer: "To fall or drop on to",
        choices: ["To fall or drop on to", "To strike", "To glide", "A soft step"]
    },
    {
        question: "What is meant by petit retires?",
        correctAnswer: "Small retire movements",
        choices: ["Small retire movements", "A step of the cat", "Retire movements", "Big retire movements"]
    },
    {
        question: "What is fouette battement?",
        correctAnswer: "A circular grand battement from 5th to 5th",
        choices: ["A circular grand battement from 5th to 5th", "A circular grand battement from 4th to 4th ", "A circular grand battement from 3rd to 3rd", "A circular grand battement from 1st to 1st"]
    },
]

const majorGrades = [
    {
        question: "What is the difference between a Battement Tendu and a Glisse?",
        correctAnswer: "A battement tendu does not leave the floor",
        choices: ["A battement tendu does not leave the floor", "A battement glisse does not leave the floor", "A battement tendu does  leave the floor", "A battement glisse does  leave the floor"]
    },
    {
        question: "How many types of releves are there?",
        correctAnswer: "2",
        choices: ["2", "4", "5", "6"]
    },
    {
        question: "What are chaines?",
        correctAnswer: "Linked half turns",
        choices: ["Linked half turns", "Linked full turns", "Whipped turn", "Turn on one leg"]
    },
    {
        question: "What is a Pas Marche?",
        correctAnswer: "A walking step",
        choices: ["A walking step", "A gliding step", "Broken step", "A spring step"]
    },
    {
        question: "What are the basic Pas de Bourrees?",
        correctAnswer: "Devant, Derriere, Under, and Over",
        choices: ["Devant, Derriere, Under, and Over", "Devant, Derriere, Left, and Right", "Front, Behind, Left, Right and Over", "Front, Behind, Under, and Over"]
    },
]